(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-11T02:01:45.510275",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
せーの
One, two
でも そんなんじゃ だーめ
But that's a no-no
もう そんなんじゃ ほーら
See, that's still not enough
心は進化するよ もーっと もーっと
My heart evolves more and more!
言葉にすれば 消えちゃう関係なら
If words would make our bond fade away,
言葉を消えばいいやって 思ってた 恐れてた
I thought it's better left unsaid.
だけど あれ? なんか違うかも
But wait, maybe it's different?
千里の道も一歩から
Every long journey starts with a single step!
石のように固いそんな意志で
With determination as hard as stone,
塵も積もればやまとなでしこ? 死ねって 癒しにきて
Even dust piles up to form a mountain!
ふわふわり ふわふわる あなたが名前を呼ぶ
Fluffily, fluffity, when you call my name,
それだけで宙へ浮浮かぶ
just that will make me float in the air.
ふわふわり ふわふわる あなたが笑っている
Fluffity, fluffily, when you show your smile,
それだけで笑顔になる
just that will make me so happy.
神様 ありがとう
Dear God, thank you!
運命のいたずらでも
Even if it's just a twist of fate,
めぐり逢えたことが 幸せなの
I'm so glad we were able to meet.
でも そんなんじゃ だーめ
But that's a no-no,
もう そんなんじゃ ほーら
see, that's still not enough!
心は進化するよ もーっと もーっと
My heart evolves more and more!
そう そんなんじゃ やだ
Yup, that's a no-go,
ねえ そんなんじゃ まだ
hey, that's a bit too early!
私のこと 見ててね ずっと ずっと
Don't take your eyes off me, never and ever!
せーの♪
One, two...
でもそんなんじゃダメ
But that's no good,
もうそんなんじゃほら
Look, it won't work.
心は進化するよ もーっと もーっと
Our hearts will keep on evolving, more and more.
言葉にすれば消えちゃう関係なら
If words will ruin our relationship,
言葉を消せばいいやって
then we won't need them.
思ってた? 恐れてた?
Don't you think so? Are you scared?
だけど あれ? なんか違うかも..
But wait. Something's not right.
千里の道も一歩から
A journey of a thousand miles starts with a single step,
石のようにかたい そんな意志で
with a resolve as hard as stone.
「し」抜きで いや 死ぬ気で!
Doing my best—no, fighting for my life!
あなたが名前を呼ぶ 穹へ浮かぶ
When you call my name, I float up to the sky.
あなたが笑っている 笑顔になる
When you smile, I smile too.
神様 ありがとう
Thank you, God.
運命のいたずらでも
Even if it's a prank by fate,
めぐり逢えたことが 幸せなの
I'm so happy we met.
でもそんなんじゃダメ
But that's no good.
もうそんなんじゃほら
Look, it won't work.
心は進化するよ もーっと もーっと
Our hearts keep evolving, more and more.
そう そんなんじゃいやーだ
Yeah, I don't want it like that.
ねえ そんなんじゃまーだ
Hey, that's not enough.
私のこと見ていてね ずっと ずっと
Look at me forever and ever.
ふわふわり ふわふわ魯
Fluffy and fluttering, fluttery and fluffy,
あなたが名前を呼ぶ それだけで宙へ浮く
I can float to the sky just by you calling my name.
ふわふわ魯 ふわふわり
Fluttery and fluffy, fluffy and fluttering,
あなたが笑っている それだけで笑顔になる
When you smile, I become all smiles too.
神様 ありがとう
Thank you, God.
運命のいたずらでも
Even if it's a prank by fate,
めぐり逢えたことが 幸せなの
I'm so happy we met.
でもそんなんじゃダメ
But that's no good.
もうそんなんじゃほら
Look, it won't work.
心は進化するよ もーっと もーっと
Our hearts keep evolving, more and more.
そう そんなんじゃいやーだ
Yeah, I don't want it like that.
ねえ そんなんじゃまーだ
Hey, that's not enough.
私のこと見ていてね ずっと ずっと
Look at me forever and ever.
ふー
Whew.
um... hello.
um... my name is Ouro Kronii. I heard that people enjoyed my first appearance before, and I'm really thankful for that.
so... this time, I wanted to sing for you guys, if it's okay, that is.
um... as for where we are right now... I'm not really sure where I am at the moment.
It seems sort of grand,
which makes me kind of self-conscious.
I... um... never sang Renai Circulation up until now,
since I never thought I could manage to do songs that are cute and,
how should I say... fuwa fuwa? I- I hope it sounds okay.
how should I say... fuwa-fuwa? I—I hope it sounds okay.
um... I wonder if I'm missing anything else? Oh, right!
be sure to use the hashtag #HELLOHALO.
I came up with it myself. I- I thought I was being pretty clever. What's happening? What? What's going on?
I came up with it myself. I—I thought I was being pretty clever... What's happening? What? What's going on?
Oh, wait. Am I dead? What did I do? Why? All of a sudden?
Well, I mean, bright side... at least this means that I was nice enough to end up here.
Well, I mean, bright side... at least this means I was nice enough to end up here.
Well, that's- that's good. Regardless, I still prepared, so I'm gonna perform,
Well, that's—that's good. Regardless, I still prepared, so I'm gonna perform...
'cause I want to give back to you guys, live or dead, so... Yeah, I hope you like it.
アイ、ウエ、オカシ、シタ
A, B, C, D, everything sweet,
カキ クッケ コンナ ニモ
F, G, H, I, just here for me.
サシスセソ ソフトクリーム
K, L, M, N, oh, lots of ice cream.
ゴゾウ ロップ デ イコウ
My four humors tells me so.
タッチ ツイテ トルテ キタ
After baking, I made a torte. What—
ナニ？ ヌネ ノリ ショウ
With salt on the top.
ハ ヒ フ ヘ ホット パイ ト
Oh, let's have some hot pie together,
ミンナ デ ヌクヌク
it would be so much fun.
ショートケーキ フワリ、キャンディ ペロペロ
Light and fluffy shortcake. Plenty of candy to lick.
あいうえ お菓子した
A B C D, everything sweet
かきくけ こんなにも
F G H I, just here for me
さしすせ ソフトクリーム
K L M N, oh, so much ice cream
五臓六腑でいこう
That's what my four humors tell me
たちつて トルテ切った
Light and fluffy shortcake
なにぬね のり塩
Plenty of candy to lick
はひふへ ホットパイと
Sitting by a river of chocolate
みんなでぬくぬく
I gaze at cotton candy clouds
ショートケーキ フワリ
Ice cream and oh! Pudding at a castle
キャンディ ペロペロ
Custard Watanuki
チョコレートの川で 綿菓子雲見た
We meet up together and go
アイスクリームと プリンのお城で
A parfait-coloured sundae
カスタード渡ぬき 二人のランデブー
Sweet beans to make me happy
パフェ色サンデー あんこがハッピー
Taiyaki and cream
たい焼きにクリーム 小悪魔ドロップ
Feisty little lemon drops
カップケーキから 苺あみつまで
Cupcakes are here
国境無しスイーツ 仲良くなれるよ
Strawberry jam over there
ぼんやり夢見れてごらん
This boundless kingdom of sweets
キャラメルみたいにくっつこう
Will bring us closer together
まみむめ モンブラン
Gaze into space and dream a little while
やゆよえ ヨーグルト
Stick together in a sweet caramel pile
らりるれ ロールケーキ
P Q R S T, tasty Mont Blanc
渡ぬきとキスを
U V W X, yogurt
ミルフィーユ ワッフル ボンボンムース
Eat up a Swiss roll and a kiss for Watanuki
モンスーン渡ぬきパイ
Jam cake so yummy
シュークリーム バナナゼリーババロア
Ocean seaweed
バラボラ渡ぬき
Toasty pot pie to warm all of us up inside
ホットケーキ バームクーヘン
Having an early lunch
ワタヌキ ワタヌキ
Early, eating toasted seaweed
みたいに靴こう
Stick together in a sweet caramel pile
まみむめ モンブラン
P Q R S T - tasty Mont Blanc
やゆよえ ヨーグルト
U V W X - yogurt
らりるれ ロールケーキ
Eat up a Swiss roll
渡ぬきとキスを
And a kiss for Watanuki
ミルクフィーユ ワッフル
Jam cake so yummy
ボンボンムース
Ocean seaweed
シュークリーム バナナゼリー
Toasty pot pie
ババロア渡ぬき
To warm all of us up inside
ホットケーキ バームクーヘン
Having an early lunch
渡ぬき渡ぬき
Early, eating toasted seaweed
バター渡ぬき クレープ
There's rolling onigiri
渡ぬき渡ぬき
Friends are so very warm
渡ぬきとごはん
Now, some autumn manju
渡ぬきとおやつ
Sweet bean bread moon
渡ぬきと肉まん
Starting with Watanuki
渡ぬきと北京ダック
Ending day with Watanuki
みつめ渡ぬき 渡ぬきシロップ
Together, let's take a look at the sun
のんびり早弁 焼きのりあぶって
It's bittersweet, and it is setting!
友達ほかほか 紅葉まんじゅうと
After baking, I made a torte...
あんぱんお月さま 渡ぬきに始まり
With salt on the top.
渡ぬきに終わる日々
Oh, let's have some hot pie together,
ほのかに見つめてごらん
It would be so much fun.
甘くて苦い夕焼を
P Q R S - tasty Mont Blanc
たちつて トルテ切った
U V W X - yogurt
なにぬね のり塩
European Swiss roll
はひふへ ホットパイと
And a kiss for Watanuki.
みんなでぬくぬく
Millefeuille, waffle, bon-bon mousse
まみむめ モンブラン
Only him, pie.
やゆよえ ヨーグルト
Cream puffs, banana jelly bavarois
らりるれ ロールケーキ
Watanuki.
渡ぬきとキスを
Pancakes, baumkuchen
ミルフィーユ ワッフル
Watanuki, Watanuki
ボンボンムース
Butter crepe Watanuki
モンスーン渡ぬきパイ
Watanuki, Watanuki
シュークリーム バナナゼリー
Meals with Watanuki
ババロア渡ぬき
Snacks with Watanuki
ホットケーキ バームクーヘン
Meat buns with Watanuki
渡ぬき渡ぬき
Peking ducks with Watanuki
バター渡ぬき クレープ
Mitsumame Watanuki
渡ぬき渡ぬき
Sweet Watanuki syrup
渡ぬきとごはん
Golden time Watanuki
渡ぬきとおやつ
Extra Watanuki rice bowl
渡ぬきと肉まん
All of my memories are well-done
渡ぬきと北京ダック
Melting, super sweet like bee's honey
みつめ渡ぬき 渡ぬきシロップ
A B C D, everything sweet
金時渡ぬき 大盛り渡ぬきどん
F G H I, just here for me
こんがり 想い出色
K L M N, oh, lots of ice cream
はちみつみたいにとろける
My four humors tells me so
あいうえ お菓子した
After baking, I made a torte...
かきくけ こんなにも
With salt on the top.
さしすせ ソフトクリーム
Oh, let's have some hot pie together,
五臓六腑でいこう
It would be so much fun.
たちつて トルテ切った
P Q R S - tasty Mont Blanc
なにぬね のり塩
U V W X - yogurt
はひふへ ホットパイと
A B C D - European Swiss roll
二人でぬくぬく
And a kiss for Watanuki.
まみむめ モンブラン
Watanuki's sugar sweet taste
やゆよえ ヨーグルト
And Watanuki's bitter side
らりるれ ロールケーキ
And Watanuki's sour side
渡ぬきとキスを
Makes us a lovely pair.
ミルフィーユ ワッフル
Millefeuille, waffle
ボンボンムース 渡ぬきパイ
Bon-bon mousse, Watanuki pie
シュークリーム バナナゼリー
Cream puffs, banana jelly
ババロア 渡ぬき
Bavarois, Watanuki
ホットケーキ バームクーヘン
Pancakes, baumkuchen
渡ぬき 渡ぬき
Watanuki, Watanuki
バター渡ぬき クレープ
Butter crepe Watanuki
渡ぬき 渡ぬき
Watanuki, Watanuki
渡ぬきとごはん
Meals with Watanuki
渡ぬきとおやつ
Snacks with Watanuki
渡ぬきと肉まん
Meat buns with Watanuki
渡ぬきと北京ダック
Peking ducks with Watanuki
みつめ渡ぬき 渡ぬきシロップ
Mitsumame Watanuki, sweet Watanuki syrup
金時渡ぬき 大盛り渡ぬきどん
Golden time Watanuki, extra Watanuki rice bowl
こんがり 想い出色
All of my memories are well-done
はちみつみたいにとろける
Melting, super sweet like bee's honey
あいうえ お菓子した
A B C D, everything sweet
かきくけ こんなにも
F G H I, just here for me
さしすせ ソフトクリーム
K L M N, oh, lots of ice cream
五臓六腑でいこう
My four humors tells me so
たちつて トルテ切った
After baking, I made a torte...
なにぬね のり塩
With salt on the top
はひふへ ホットパイと
Oh, let's have some hot pie together
二人でぬくぬく
It would be so much fun
まみむめ モンブラン
P Q R S T, tasty Mont Blanc
やゆよえ ヨーグルト
U V W X, yogurt
らりるれ ロールケーキ
Eat up a Swiss roll
渡ぬきとキスを
And a kiss for Watanuki
渡ぬきの甘味と 渡ぬきの苦味
Watanuki's sugar sweet taste and bitter side
渡ぬきの酸味で
And Watanuki's sour side
スキスキ ラボコンボ
Makes us a lovely pair
あいうえ お菓子した
A B C D, everything sweet
かきくけ こんなにも
F G H I, just here for me
さしすせ ソフトクリーム
K L M N, oh, so much ice cream
五臓六腑でいこう
That's what my four humors tell me
たちつて トルテ切った
Light and fluffy shortcake
なにぬね のり塩
Plenty of candy to lick
はひふへ ホットパイと
Sitting by a river of chocolate
二人でぬくぬく
I gaze at cotton candy clouds
まみむめ モンブラン
Gaze into space and dream a little while
やゆよえ ヨーグルト
Stick together in a sweet caramel pile
らりるれ ロールケーキ
P Q R S T, tasty Mont Blanc
渡ぬきとキスを
U V W X, yogurt
ミルフィーユ ワッフル
Eat up a Swiss roll
ボンボンムース 渡ぬきパイ
And a kiss for Watanuki
シュークリーム バナナゼリー
Jam cake so yummy
ババロア 渡ぬき
Ocean seaweed
ホットケーキ バームクーヘン
Toasty pot pie
渡ぬき 渡ぬき
To warm all of us up inside
バター渡ぬき クレープ
Having an early lunch
渡ぬき 渡ぬき
Early, eating toasted seaweed
渡ぬきとごはん
There's rolling onigiri
渡ぬきとおやつ
Friends are so very warm
渡ぬきと肉まん
Now, some autumn manju
渡ぬきと北京ダック
Sweet bean bread moon
みつめ渡ぬき 渡ぬきシロップ
Starting with Watanuki
金時渡ぬき 大盛り渡ぬきどん
Ending day with Watanuki
こんがり 想い出色
Together, let's take a look at the sun
はちみつみたいにとろける
It's bittersweet, and it is setting!
あいうえ お菓子した
After baking, I made a torte...
かきくけ こんなにも
With salt on the top
さしすせ ソフトクリーム
Oh, let's have some hot pie together
五臓六腑でいこう
It would be so much fun
スキスキ ラブコンボ
Makes us a lovely pair
交わした約束忘れないよ
I won't forget the promises we exchanged,
目を閉じ確かめる
I close my eyes to affirm it.
押し寄せた闇振り払って進むよ
I will shake off the overwhelming darkness to move forward.
いつになったらなくした未来を
When will I ever be able to see
私ここでまた見ることができるの?
the lost future from here again?
溢れ出した不安の影を何度も裂いて
Shattering the overflowing shadows of anxiety again and again,
この世界歩んでこう
let's move forward in this world.
とどめなく刻まれた時は今始まり告げ
Time now begins to tick away incessantly,
変わらない思いをのせ 閉ざされた扉開けよう
let's open the closed door with our unchanging feelings.
目覚めた心は走り出した未来を描くため
My heart awakes in order to depict the future,
難しい道で立ち止まっても
even if I come to a halt on a tough road.
空はきれいな青さでいつも待っていてくれるから怖くない
The blue sky always waits for me, so I'm not afraid.
もう何があっても挫けない
I won't be disheartened no matter what.
振り返れば仲間がいて
When I looked back, my friends were there,
気がつけば優しく包まれてた
and before I knew it, I was surrounded by kindness.
何もかもが歪んだ世界で唯一信じれるここが救いだった
In a distorted world, this was the only place I could believe in.
喜びも悲しみもわけあえば強まる想い
My feelings become stronger if we share joy and sadness.
この声が届くのなら きっと奇跡はおこせるだろう
If this voice reaches you, I'm sure a miracle will happen.
交わした約束忘れないよ 目を閉じ確かめる
I won't forget the promises we exchanged; I close my eyes.
押し寄せた闇振り払って進むよ
I will shake off the overwhelming darkness to move forward.
どんなに大きな壁があっても
No matter how big the wall is,
越えてみせるからきっと
I'll definitely overcome it.
明日信じて祈って 壊れた世界で彷徨えて私は
Believing and praying for tomorrow in a broken world...
引き寄せられるように辿り着いた
I arrived as if I was being drawn.
目覚めた心は走り出した未来を描くため
My heart awakes in order to depict the future.
交わした約束忘れないよ
I won't forget the promise we made,
目を閉じ確かめる
closing my eyes to be sure.
押し寄せた闇振り払って
Shaking off the surging darkness,
進むよ
I will move forward!
繰り返せば仲間がいて
When I look back, my friends are there,
気が付けば優しく包まれてた
and before I knew it, I was wrapped in warmth.
何もかもが歪んだ世界で
In a world where everything is distorted,
唯一信じられるここが救いだった
this place I could believe in was my only salvation.
喜びも悲しみも分け合えば強まる想い
If we share joy and sorrow, our feelings grow stronger.
この声が届くのならきっと奇跡は起こせるだろう
If this voice can reach you, I'm sure we can work a miracle!
交わした約束忘れないよ
I won't forget the promise we made,
目を閉じ確かめる
closing my eyes to be sure.
どんなに大きな壁があっても
No matter how big the wall in our way,
越えてみせるからきっと
I will surely overcome it!
明日を信じて祈って
Believe in tomorrow and pray.
壊れた世界でさ迷っては
Wandering through a broken world,
私は引き寄せられるようにたどり着いた
I arrived here as if drawn to it.
覚めた心は走り出した未来を描くため
An awakened heart started running to paint the future.
難しい道で立ち止まっても空はきれいな青さで
Even if I stop on a difficult road, the blue sky is pure.
いつも待っていてくれるだから怖くない
It always waits for me, so I'm not afraid.
もう何があっても挫けない
No matter what happens, I won't give up.
目覚めた心は走り出した
An awakened heart started running
未来を描くため難しい道で立ち止まっても
to paint the future, even stopping on a tough path.
空はきれいな青さでいつも待っていてくれる
The pure blue sky always waits for me,
だから怖くない
so I'm not afraid.
もう何があっても挫けない
No matter what happens, I won't give up.
ずっと明日を待って
Waiting for tomorrow, always.
Hey, what are you doing here again?
Are you trying to upstage me here, of all places?
Um... I don't think it comes off.
Well, you know, I refuse to let that happen, after all, I'm Ouro Kronii!
Are you seeing what I'm seeing right now?
Oh jeez.
You two down there, yes, you!
Uh, hello? I'm right here. Uh, rude.
One of you does not belong here.
Oh. Yeah, that's right.
Get out of here!
Uh, yeah, whatever you want to believe, I guess.
Anyway, behold, a stage more fitting for the likes of you.
Oh. I mean, of course.
Of course, I'm the more angelic and kind-hearted one, of course.
Oh man, you are so based!
Thank you guys. Thank you.
Oh.
Oh man,
bless... love.
Thank you.
Wait...
I'm the devil?
Bro, she should be blind for real, for real!
Like me? That doesn't make any sense.
What?
Hey, come over here.
Yeah, you... yeah, come here.
What are you looking at?
Huh? Stupid little thing, huh?
Smug? You like that, huh?
Oh, you're just a little wannabe of mine.
You know what? I don't like you.
Get out of here!
God, always wanna take the spotlight for some reason. Disgusting.
I mean, at least I still look pretty damn good.
Sheesh!
Haha!
Oh, okay.
Here we go.
あたし ヴァンパイヤ
I am a vampire
いいの？ 吸っちゃっていいの？
Can I suck from you?
「もう無理 もう無理」なんて悪い子だね
"You've had enough," I thought bad boys like it rough?
試したい ないっぱい で吐き出したい まだ絶対いけるよ
I wanna go beyond, 'til I spit and cough it up, I just know I can take even more
最低 最高 ずっと いき込んできている
Rocking back and forth, between the bad and the best
甘くなる 不安の果実
And now the fruit of anxiety is ripe
no more 発展 嫉妬 息をしても
No more moving on, the jealousy in your chest
要らない だけ留守泥だけ
It can't keep down, so cast it all aside!
誰かといれば それはそれなら
If only there was someone, it's too late so there's no one
強がってたって気持ちに逆らえない
Though my outer self is tough, I can't ignore the voice inside
離れていても 感じてるエモ
Even when we are lonely, emotions that I'm feeling
繋がって確かめたら 死ぬかも
If we connected and checked, I think I'd pass away
いいもん 悲しいもん 切ないもん
That's fine by me, feel it mourning, feel it hurting
きみのすべてを 噛らうまで 絶叫
It's never gonna stop until I eat you up, screaming!
あたし ヴァンパイヤ
I am a vampire
いいの？ 吸っちゃっていいの？
Can I suck from you?
「もう無理 もう無理」なんて悪い子だね
"You've had enough," I thought bad boys like it rough?
試したい ないっぱい で吐き出したい まだ絶対いけるよ
I wanna go beyond, 'til I spit and cough it up, I just know I can take even more
あたし ヴァンパイヤ
I am a vampire
求めちゃってまた枯らしちゃってほらやな感じ
Keeping me waiting, with the mood deflating, that won't sit right with me
泣いて忘れた 「はじめまして」
Sobbing while losing the memory of “How nice of us to meet!”
あたし ヴァンパイヤ
I am a vampire
愛情をください まだ絶対いけるよ
Please love me all the while, I just know I can take even more
あたし ヴァンパイヤ まずはこっち向いて
I am a vampire, I'll let you strike first if you dare
内緒の想い洗いざらい吐き出したなら「正に」ばっかり
When everything that I was hiding came out of me, it was exactly right!
割り切れないけど 余りじゃない
It's plain to see, not enough to sway me
そっと朝まで通せんぼう
Quietly I'll bear it all through the night
繰り返すヤダ 我儘はタダ
The repeating denials, no price on selfish styles
欲張ってまたチャンスを逃すの
Letting chances pass me by, 'cause I bit off more than I can chew
病まない もし叶えたいけど
This constant wishful thinking, why can't it start existing
重なって押しつぶされちゃうのかも
It'll keep building up 'til I'm crushed under the weight
いいもん 悲しいもん 切ないもん
That's fine by me, feel it mourning, feel it hurting
きみのすべてを 噛らうまで
It's never gonna stop until I eat you up
いいじゃん 楽しいじゃん 気持ちいいじゃん
It's fine! And it's fun right? Feeling good right?
溺れるまで癖になるね 絶叫
It's addicting, holding back your breath before you drown, screaming!
あたし ヴァンパイヤ
I am a vampire
いいの？ 吸っちゃっていいの？
Can I suck from you?
「もう無理 もう無理」なんて悪い子だね
"You've had enough," I thought bad boys like it rough?
試したい ないっぱい で吐き出したい まだ絶対いけるよ
I wanna go beyond, 'til I spit and cough it up, I just know I can take even more
きみも ヴァンパイヤ
And you're a vampire! So you can suck from me
いいよ 吸っちゃっていいよ
Make me say I've had enough, make me love it when you're rough
「もう無理 もう無理」だって言わせてほしい
Cause you're the only one, the only one for me!
きみ以外では絶対にいけないほら絶讃させてよ
How many times now has it been?
きみも ヴァンパイヤ
Seeing stars in our eyes and bubbles trapping you and me
求めちゃってまた枯らしちゃって今何回目？
And you're a vampire! C'mon give me overtime!
星が見えるような泡の中で
I just know I can go take more!
きみも ヴァンパイヤ
You are vampire, I'll let you strike first if you dare
延長をください まだ絶対いけるよ
I just know we can take even more
あたし ヴァンパイヤ まずはこっち向いて
I am a vampire, first look over here
内緒の想い洗いざらい吐き出したなら
When everything I was hiding came pouring out
割り切れないけど余りじゃない
It's not enough to sway me, but I can't let it go
そっと朝まで通せんぼう
Quietly blocking the way until morning
繰り返すヤダ 我儘はタダ
Repeating denials, selfishness is free
欲張ってまたチャンスを逃すの
Letting chances slip away by being greedy
病まない もし叶えたいけど
Wishing it wouldn't hurt, even if I want it granted
重なって押しつぶされちゃうのかも
Maybe I'll just get crushed under the weight
いいもん 悲しいもん 切ないもん
That's fine, that's sad, that's painful
きみのすべてを 噛らうまで
Until I devour everything about you
いいじゃん 楽しいじゃん 気持ちいいじゃん
It's fine, it's fun, it feels good
溺れるまで癖になるね 絶叫
Becoming an addiction until we drown, screaming!
あたし ヴァンパイヤ
I am a vampire
いいの？ 吸っちゃっていいの？
Can I suck from you?
「もう無理 もう無理」なんて悪い子だね
"You've had enough," I thought bad boys like it rough?
試したい ないっぱい で吐き出したい まだ絶対いけるよ
I wanna go beyond, 'til I spit and cough it up, I just know I can take even more
きみも ヴァンパイヤ まずはこっち向いて
And you're a vampire, first look over here
絶対いけるよ
I just know we can take even more
Hi!
I wanna people say,
All right?
ジャマママンナ...
Jamamamanna...
タイトロープは崩れる 壊される
Tightropes collapse, breaking apart,
とんでレイディ
Flying lady!
ライトめがけて無様に砕かれる
Shattering dazzlingly under the light.
そんな将来
Such a future.
ハイに気ままに ロンリー ロンリー
Casually high, lonely, lonely...
空いた言葉で 弄人 囚人
Empty words, a prisoner, a captive.
愛も変わらず 後悔なんてない
Love remains unchanged, no regrets at all.
hey, it's amazing.
Yeah, it's amazing.
ディス ディス ラバ ベイビー
This, this, loving you, baby!
愛のその 迫りくる
The approaching bud of malice...
ディス ディス ラバ クレイジー
This, this, loving you, crazy!
害のその 人の目は笑い
Everyone's eyes are laughing.
あ あ いしてる
Ah, ah, doing it...
過ぎたことまで 好きすぎる
Exceeding even past limits,
ライ ライ ラビングユー そんな言葉で
Lie, lie, loving you, with those words,
そんなことして ジャマママンナ
Doing things like that, jamamamanna...
ディス ディス ラバ ベイビー
This, this, loving you, baby!
愛のその 迫りくる
The approaching bud of malice...
ディス ディス ラバ クレイジー
This, this, loving you, crazy!
害のその 人の目は笑い
Everyone's eyes are laughing.
あ あ いしてる
Ah, ah, doing it...
空中到来 ラブマニア
Mid-air arrival, love mania,
全部 泣きごと重ねて
Stacking up all the whining,
ハイファイ 恋せよ ライアイヤン
High-five, fall in love, yeah, yeah, yeah,
演技真似て 解は隠して
Mimicking acting, hiding the truth,
三つ重ねて ロンリー ロンリー
Stacking three, lonely, lonely...
きっとあなたは 弄人 囚人
Surely you are a prisoner, a captive.
愛も変わらず 後悔なんてない
Love remains unchanged, no regrets at all.
hey, it's amazing.
Yeah, it's amazing.
ディス ディス ラバ ベイビー
This, this, loving you, baby!
愛のその 迫りくる
The approaching bud of malice...
ディス ディス ラバ クレイジー
This, this, loving you, crazy!
害のその 人の目は笑い
Everyone's eyes are laughing.
あ あ いしてる
Ah, ah, doing it...
過ぎたことまで 好きすぎる
Exceeding even past limits,
ライ ライ ラビングユー そんな言葉で
Lie, lie, loving you, with those words,
そんなことして ジャマママンナ
Doing things like that, jamamamanna...
ディス ディス ラバ ベイビー
This, this, loving you, baby!
どうだっていい言を
No matter what I say,
嘘って吐いて戻れない
Lying and speaking, I can't take it back.
時効なんてやってこない
There's no time like the present.
奪ったように奪われて
Stolen as if I had stolen it,
今日だって叶わない
Today of all days won't come true.
思ったように欺けない
I can't deceive as I thought.
腐っている僕には 腐っているものが理解できない
Rotting inside, I don't understand
おいえココまで 捨てい
Throw it away, up to here.
隠して仕舞い込んだんだ
"I hid it and played it off."
メイデー 僕と分かっても
Mayday, even if you know it's me,
もう抱き締め なくて容易いんだよ
You don't need to hold me close.
hey メイデー 僕が解けたら
Hey, mayday, if you figure it out,
もう一度 嘲笑いてくれるかな
Can you laugh at me once more?
マ ボロシ だって 知るんだよ
I know I'm a mess.
嘘 憑き だって 知るんだよ ねぇ
I know it's just a lie, you see.
no だって言う筈が
Saying "no", but for some reason,
キョドってyesを声に出す
Saying "yes" out loud.
後悔の脆弱は
Regret's fragility is such that
騙したほうが正義なの
Fooling others makes you righteous.
卑怯だって構わない
Despicable? I don't mind.
祈って置いてそれは無い
Praying won't change a thing.
飾っていた舌把が 墓穴を掘って焼ける様
The decorated tongue digs its own grave.
負い目どこまで グレー
How far do bad things go, Gray?
害者ヅラしたって
Even if you act like a victim,
メイデー 僕を殴ってよ
Mayday, strike me down.
正直者が夢見たい ならば
If a righteous person wants to dream,
hey メイデー 僕を裁いてよ
Hey, mayday, judge me.
最後まで甘えてしまう のは
Yielding to indulgence till the end
亡霊だって知るんだよ
Is because I'm a ghost, I know.
空白だって知るんだよ ねぇ
It's all a void, I know, right?
足りないものを望んだら
Wishing for what's missing,
僕じゃない 僕に出会ったよ
I met someone who wasn't me.
それでも 前に進んだの
Even so, I kept moving forward.
クラクラしちゃう夜も
Even on nights that make me spin,
足りない僕を愛してよ
Love the me that lacks so much.
ego-mamaが僕を育てた の
Ego-mama raised me.
きみには僕が見えるかな
Can you see me, I wonder?
孤独なピエロが
A lonely pierrot...
メイデー 僕と分かっても
Mayday, even if you know it's me,
もう抱き締め なくて容易いんだよ
You don't need to hold me close.
hey メイデー 僕が解けたら
Hey, mayday, if you figure it out,
もう一度 嘲笑いてくれるかな
Can you laugh at me once more?
もしも君に耳があったら
If you had ears,
この歌を聴かせてあげられるのに
I could let you listen to this song.
もしも君に心があったら
If you had a heart,
この好きで包んであげられるのに
I could wrap you in this love.
ねえ 嫌いになるなら僕を殺して
Hey, if you're going to hate me, kill me.
君に愛されない僕なんかいらない
I don't need myself if I'm not loved by you.
どこにもいないいないいないない ばぁ
You're nowhere to be found, peekaboo.
もしもなんてどこにもなくて
If "what ifs" are nowhere to be found,
きっと用意されてなんかない
And surely nothing was prepared for us,
「どうしよう」＋「こうしよう」＋
"What should we do?" + "Let's do this" +
「そうしよう」＝心中会合（サミット）
"Let's do that" = Suicide Summit
とは聞こえの良い自己淘汰
That's just a nice-sounding self-elimination.
君は僕を 見ない
You don't look at me.
ねえ 嫌いになるから僕を愛して
Hey, since you're going to hate me, love me.
君に愛されたい僕はないから
Since I don't exist without your love,
どこにもいないよ ねえ痛いよ
You're nowhere to be found, hey, it hurts.
もしも君に耳があったら
If you had ears,
この歌を聴かせてあげられる
I could let you listen to this song.
もしも君に心があったら
If you had a heart,
この好きで包んであげられる
I could wrap you in this love.
キミの耳なんていらない
I don't need your ears.
キミの心だっていらない
I don't need your heart either.
キミがそうやって苦しんでる
You suffering like that—
顔が見られたらいいよ
As long as I can see your face, it's fine.
And we're back!
You know, I'm really starting to like this new me.
What do you think? Hey?
I mean, I'm starting to kind of think it's real cool.
And uh, I just realized that I didn't introduce myself properly back there. My bad!
Well, my name is Ouro Kronii, and I am the Warden of Time.
Gera ni-chi-wa!
And I, after much waiting, have finally done it. We're here, we've made it. It's taken a long time.
Kronii also apologizes for the delays, but...
Finally, my second original song, Souten ni Moyu, will be coming out soon. Sooner than you think!
And thank you so much for waiting. Um, I hope you haven't forgotten it.
But, yes, here is my second original song, Souten ni Moyu.
これは鈍色の夢か
Is this a dull-colored dream?
逸ルナと笑われて
I'm laughed at for being impatient.
噛み締めた音は消え
The sound I savored fades away,
囲む静寂、灯を灯す
Surrounding silence, lighting a lamp.
side to side 鵯 back and forth 鵯
side to side, back and forth
流されがちなこの時代
In this era prone to being swept away,
運命さえ断つんだろう
We'll probably cut off even our fate.
かき分ける人の波へ
Into the parting waves of people.
奎持を燃やして
Burning our post,
閟の声 鐘を鳴らせ
Sound the bell of the secret voice,
don't hold it back, 問う
Don't hold it back, I ask.
手が届きそうな明日なんてつまらないだろう
A tomorrow within reach would be boring, wouldn't it?
瞳は燧色
My eyes are flint-colored.
just do what's right in my sight
そう刻もうと
So that I may carve it in.
don't hold it back, 応答よ、そうだろう
Don't hold it back, give me an answer, right?
大志抱き高みまで
Holding high ambitions up to the heights,
沈む夕闇さえ彩るほどに
To the point of coloring even the sinking twilight.
限界なんて越えて行け woah
Surpass even limits, woah!
声は高々になって艶情適
Voices grow high and passionate,
刺激物を模した甘い罠
A sweet trap mimicking a stimulant.
side to side 鵯 back and forth 鵯
side to side, back and forth
流れに時に棺刺し
Sometimes piercing the coffin in the flow,
未来さえ断つんだろう
We'll probably cut off even the future.
想いを研ぎ澄ませて
Sharpening our feelings,
鋼のように固めた意志は冴えよう
Let our willpower hardened like steel shine clear.
奎持を構えて
Taking up our post,
時の声 鐘を鳴らせ
Sound the bell of the voice of time.
消さないで
Don't erase it,
煌めいて
Sparkle,
why not go all in
張り詰めていく空気が灯を滾らせる
The tightening air makes the light surge.
瞳に蒼天の色
The color of the azure sky in my eyes.
その手にかけて日時に接吻を
Kissing the date and time held in that hand.
don't hold it back, 問う
Don't hold it back, I ask.
手が届きそうな明日なんてつまらないだろう
A tomorrow within reach would be boring, wouldn't it?
瞳は燧色
My eyes are flint-colored.
just do what's right in my sight
そう刻もうと
So that I may carve it in.
don't hold it back, 応答よ、そうだろう
Don't hold it back, give me an answer, right?
大志抱き高みまで
Holding high ambitions up to the heights,
沈む夕闇さえ彩るほどに
To the point of coloring even the sinking twilight.
限界なんて越えて行け woah
Surpass even limits, woah!
奎持を構えて
Taking up our post,
時の声 鐘を鳴らせ
Sound the bell of the voice of time.
消さないで
Don't erase it,
煌めいて
Sparkle,
why not go all in
燦々 キラリ色した 大切なもの
With every little precious thing I have, glittering about,
忘れないから そう この日を
I'll never forget this day.
なんてこんな風にいこう？
Let's live just like this...
What a banger that song was!
You did great.
Um, I'm really happy seeing how energetic you are.
I'm really happy seeing how energetic you are.
I know.
No need to address the underlying fact.
Okay.
But in the end, it doesn't matter who the better one is out of us two.
But in the end, it doesn't matter
who the better one is out of us two.
We don't need to compete.
I never wanted to compete to begin with.
Because we're all made in the name of beauty and perfection,
Because we're all made in the name
of beauty and perfection,
Kronii. We're all in this together!
And what better way to become perfect than by studying the masters like me?
And what better way to become perfect
than by studying the masters like me?
Well, I got just the thing for you. Oh boy!
Bam!
My 2024 birthday merch!
Shall we take a look here?
First up, we have "Studying Matters" Rubber Mat,
First up, we have "Studying Matters"
Rubber Mat,
which is a rubber mousepad, and you can use it for your keyboard, your mouse.
a rubber mousepad for your keyboard and mouse.
You can use it for eating, for studying, like for all sorts of things, honestly.
You can use it for eating, studying,
and all sorts of things.
And with such beautiful illustration, look at that, man.
With such a beautiful illustration, look at that!
And next up, we have "Plan with Me" Whiteboard Stand, which is a whiteboard stand with other bunch of cute chibi illustrations.
And next up, we have "Plan with Me"
Whiteboard Stand, with cute chibi illustrations.
This is very useful. You can use it to write down my net stream
This is very useful for writing down stream notes
or for your work, or for your school. It's very um it's very flexible.
or for your work or school. It's very flexible,
You can use it for whatever.
and you can use it for whatever you want.
So, um I'm I'm really excited.
So, I'm really excited!
And next up, we have "Maid for Me" Pencil Case, which is a pencil case in the form of a plushie. You can put all your important supplies there like, you know, pens, pencils, erasers,
Next, we have the "Maid for Me" Pencil Case,
a plush pencil case for all your supplies—
or, you know, if you're really desperate, you can actually use it as a plushie. Put some stuffing into it
pens, pencils, erasers. Or, if you're desperate,
you can stuff it and use it as a plushie!
And bam! You got yourself a plushie. Let's go!
Bam, you've got yourself a plushie. Let's go!
And next, we have "Write with Me" Pencil, which is a mechanical pencil, um of course, since it's a mechanical pencil, this is going to be reusable
Next, we have the "Write with Me" Pencil,
a reusable mechanical pencil,
and 0.5 millimeters, very accessible, um for people
0.5 mm in size, making it very accessible
because it's a very common uh size length. So yeah, it's it's awesome.
since it's a common size. So yeah, it's awesome!
Look look forward to it. Boros is so cute. Look at that. Look at him. No thoughts, head empty as usual.
Boros is so cute on it! Look at him—
no thoughts, head empty as usual.
And next up, we also have a voice pack, which is relevant to the theme "Study with Me" And this is an English talking about how to use your time well.
And next up, we have a voice pack themed around
"Study with Me," featuring English talk
I think it's good, obviously, cuz it's done by me.
on how to use your time well. It's great,
So do check it out. And that's not it. That's there's more. That's right.
obviously, because it's by me, so check it out!
And there's more, that's right!
Next up, we have a full set purchase bonus, and you can have this beautiful illustration as a postcard, which is going to be so cute.
Next, we have a full set purchase bonus:
a postcard featuring this beautiful illustration.
And what's more, um for limited quantity, it's going to be hand-signed by yours truly.
And what's more, in limited quantities,
it will be hand-signed by yours truly!
So be sure to get it as soon as possible if you want to get um hand signatures from me.
So be sure to grab it as soon as possible
if you want a hand-signed one from me.
Um, hand signatures from me! That's right!
Hand signatures from me, that's right!
And all of this is going to go on sale right after this wonderful little live we got here.
All of this goes on sale right after
this wonderful little live stream!
Yeah. And you buy it too, yeah?
Yeah, you'll buy it too, right?
Good, good. Okay. Well, come over here.
I got a little something to tell you. Here. Put your hand against mine.
I have a little something to tell you.
Here, put your hand against mine.
Huh?
Let's take, you're lovin' it,
Vegetable juice.
You must love this drink, I decided now,
So take now, with my true heart, vegetable juice.
It costs just two dollars! Yay!
Come on! Come on!
Let's dance!
Mellow and mellow, vegetable juice,
Creamy and creamy, vegetable juice.
I guess you should like the best this one, big pale blue juice!
We are vegetarian,
Every vegetarian,
Happy vegetarian,
Y-A-S-A-I, love you, so and I love you!
Let's take, you're lovin' it,
Vegetable juice.
You must love this drink, I decided now,
So take now, with my true heart,
Vegetable juice.
It costs just two dollars!
Come on! Come on!
Let's dance!
Mellow and mellow, vegetable juice,
Creamy and creamy, vegetable juice.
I guess you should like the best this one, big pale blue juice!
We are vegetarian,
Every vegetarian,
Happy vegetarian,
Y-A-S-A-I, love you, so and I love you!
You know what? Let's never do that again.
Um, yeah, that was kind of weird.
I thought it was a good idea initially.
Anyway, thanks for watching my live! Our live! Bye-bye!
HELLO HALO Ouro Kronii's 2024 Birthday Celebration